

Liridon Ceka

Date of birth: 19 Feb 1992

Nationality: Macedonian/citizen of the Republic of North Macedonia

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Murat Baftijari Nr12, 1200 Tetovo, North Macedonia

LC18136@seeu.edu.mk

Advokat.Ceka@gmail.com

(+389) 78282158

LinkedIn: https://

www.linkedin.com/in/liridon-

ceka-61a432123/ Facebook: https:// www.facebook.com/ Liridon.Cekaa/

Whatsapp Messenger: +389

78 282 158

Viber: +389 78 282 158

ABOUT ME

An MSc in International Law and Human Rights, a graduate of Law University and participant in many seminars, workshops as well as summer schools. Winner of "Konrad Adenauer Stiftung" Scholarship. I have worked as an attorney within the mid-sized, general practice law firms in my hometown, basic court and in different judicial matters like translating and interpretation. I have handled an array of litigation and legal matters, representing the interests of corporate and individual clients on complex issues, transactions, agreements, and lawsuits. and actively I've been involved in coordinating project schedules, resources, equipment, workforce, financial aspects, payroll and payable management. Liaising with clients to identify and define project requirements, scope, and objectives. Assisting the Project Manager in the daily tasks and properly organizing the operational and technical aspects of the project. I've also worked as a Consultant in particular for analysing project data, determine potential risks and develop appropriate mitigation plans. I've provided project control support and successfully planned and executed assigned projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

15 OCT 2021 - CURRENT - Tetovo, North Macedonia

Consultant

Ecolog International FZE

- Conducted research, surveys and interviews to gain understanding of the business
- Analysed statistics
- Detecting issues and investigating ways to resolve them
- Assessing the pros and cons of possible strategies
- Compiling and presenting information orally, visually and in writing
- Making recommendations for improvement, using computer models to test them and presenting findings to client
- Developing and implementing new procedures or training.

12 AUG 2021 - 14 OCT 2021 - Tetovo, North Macedonia

Accounts Payable Payroll

Ecolog Deutschland GmbH

- Calculate, post business transactions, process invoices, verify financial data for use in maintaining accounts payable records, and provide other clerical support necessary to pay the obligations of the organization
- Clarify any questionable invoice items, prices or receiving signatures
- Obtain proper information and/or data regarding invoice payments
- Assemble invoices to be completed for payment
- Verify and calculate all extensions and totals on invoices (calculating and taking discounts when applicable),
- Review invoices and requisitions for satisfactory payment approval
- Check vendor files for any previous payments and assign voucher numbers
- Maintain copies of vouchers, invoices or correspondence necessary for files
- Prepare vouchers listing invoice number, date, vendor address, item description, amounts and coding per accounting policies and procedures
- Type periodic reports and other records

19 JUN 2019 - 11 AUG 2021 - Mazar e Sharif, Afghanistan

Operations Project Coordinator

Ecolog International FZE

- Maintaining and monitoring project plans, project schedules, work hours, budgets and expenditures.
- Documenting and following up on important actions and decisions from the Project Manager and the Higher Management.
- Preparing necessary presentation materials for meetings.
 Ensuring project deadlines are met.
- Determining project changes.
- Providing administrative support as needed, especially to the Finance dept and HR
- Undertaking project tasks as required.
- Developing project strategies.
- Ensuring projects adhere to frameworks and all documentation is maintained appropriately for each project.
- Assess project risks and issues and provide solutions where applicable.
- Create a project management calendar for fulfilling each goal and objective.
- Preparing and submitting to the higher management the Daily, Weekly and Monthly reports/data of the operational aspect of the Project.
- Tracking all the above in SAP Software and maintaining the same.

12 NOV 2018 - 18 JUN 2019 - Kabul, Afghanistan

Contracts Administrator

Ecolog International FZE

- As a Contract Administrator I had the below duties and responsibilities:
- Liaising with staff on all levels of company to analyze and determine comprehensive contract strategy.
- Designing standardized language and guidelines for contracts.
 Reviewing contracts for compliance with language guidelines.
- Collaborating with internal procurement, operations team in different sites in Afghanistan and human resources teams to ensure contracts' and newly awarded Individual Service Request compliance.
- Dealing with NSPA(NATO Support and Procurement Agency) in daily basis, communicating and preventing NCR(Noncompliance reports) to be opened against the company.
- Contracts Management is the POC to all the potential clients in all Afghanistan, this meant coordinating and being in constant touch with the clients, whether they are the US Army, private firms and corporations, NATO, Bundeswehr, and many other private and government subsidized agencies.
- Sharing and clarifying contract processes, conditions and details with management, business partners and employees.
- Obtaining contract-related information from relevant parties.
 Reviewing contracts, verifying accuracy and resolving discrepancies in line with company rules and guidelines.
- Ensuring relevant documentation accompany contracts
 Tracking and archiving properly the contracts.

 Creating Contracts using SAP Software and tracking the contracts and newly Awarded works until the service is completed and the clients requirements are satisfied.

7 NOV 2017 - 17 OCT 2018 - Tetovo, North Macedonia **Associate Attorney**

Freelance

- As an Associate Lawyer, I worked in cooperation with senior Lawyers and Bailiffs in my hometown, since I am not fully licensed to represent the clients in courts. Some of my duties included and were not limited to the below.
- Advise and assist the senior lawyer represents clients in courts, before government agencies, and in private legal matters.
- Communicate with clients, colleagues, judges, and others involved in the case.
- Conduct research and analysis of legal problems. Interpret laws, rulings, and regulations for individuals and businesses.
- Present facts in writing and verbally to the clients or others, and argue on behalf of the client.
- Prepare and file legal documents, such as lawsuits, appeals, wills, contracts, and deeds.

8 AUG 2015 – 13 MAR 2017 – Skopje, North Macedonia **Editorial translator**

RTV 21 DOEL

- I was a chief translator in Radio Television 21 and used to supervise a team of three interpreters and journalists. I was assigned as an instant voice emitted translator for high ranking guests (Deputies, Ministries, Prime Ministers) in different political debates and election night programs.
- Translating Regional and Worldwide news from Macedonian/ English and German to Albanian and vice versa.

27 MAY 2012 – 4 JAN 2015 – Skopje, North Macedonia

Secretary General

NGO "Jusuf Bageri"

- As secretary-general, I supported the Chair in ensuring the smooth functioning of the Management . I was responsible for ensuring meetings are effectively organized and recorded.
- Maintaining effective records and administration.

26 MAY 2012 - CURRENT - Tetovo, North Macedonia

Judicial Translator & Court Interpreter

Laureta Ceka Judicial Translating Office

- As a interpreter I used to convert information from one language into another language, more specifically, I was a interpreter of three languages, Albanian/Macedonian/English.
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.

5 FEB 2012 - 17 MAY 2012 - Tetovo, North Macedonia

Administrative Assistant

"Naxhi Zeqiri Notary Office"

- Administer oaths and affirmations Assisting the Notary on briefings, schedules and managed the time-sheets. Maintaining the office workplace by handling documents, invoices, statements, etc.
- Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.
- Brought forth an exceptional work ethic and commitment to company values.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

9 SEP 2015 – 12 SEP 2018 – Street Ilinden bb 1200, Tetovo, North Macedonia

Mr.Sc of International Law and International Relations

State University of Tetovo - Law Faculty/Postgraduate Studies

https://unite.edu.mk/en/

5 SEP 2010 – 28 OCT 2013 – Ilindenska 335 , Tetovo, North Macedonia

Bachelor of Law

South European University - Law Faculty

Field(s) of study

Law

Graduated with high honors, average GPA 8.5. | https://www.seeu.edu.mk/

PUBLICATIONS

International Migration and the rights of refugees in EU

2018

Master Thesis

"RELIGION, ETHNICITY AND NATIONALISM"

2015 https://www.kas.de/documents/ 281657/281706/7_file_storage_file_18024_2.pdf/5737d25abcbb-418e-5ed4-9deff7d0b918?version=1.0&t=1539652051452 The role of nationalism in the triangle between nation, state and religion (Macedonia)

https://www.kas.de/documents/ 281657/281706/7 file storage file 18024 2.pdf/5737d25abcbb-418e-5ed4-9deff7d0b918?version=1.0&t=1539652051452

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Albanian | Macedonian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

German

Listening B2	Reading C2	Spoken production B1	Spoken interaction B1	Writing C2
English				
Listening C2	Reading C2	Spoken production C2	Spoken interaction C2	Writing C2
Croatian				
Listening C2	Reading C2	Spoken production C1	Spoken interaction B2	Writing B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office: proficient user of Word, Excel and Powerpoint / SAP MDM / - SAP Intermediate / SAP ERP (FICO MM Success Factors) / SAP WMS / SAP JAM / Communication software and social media / Google tools (Gmail Drive Google forms etc)

VOLUNTEERING

Volunteer at IDEA Group

Skopje/Macedonia

Volunteer at American Corner

Tetovo/Macedonia

Volunteer at CIVIL

Skopje/Macedonia

Volunteeer at Green Aktion

Zagreb/Croatia

Volunteer at Konrad Adenauer Foundation

Skopje/North Macedonia

CONFERENCES AND SEMINARS

> Spli/Croatia

Climate Changes and their consequences - Balkan Youth Climate Movement

> Tetovo/Macedonia

Protecting Human Rights - USAID

> Skopje/ Macedonia

CIVIL - Be a Civil journalist

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: AM

Driving Licence: A1

Driving Licence: B1

Driving Licence: B

I would love the chance to further discuss the position and what skills I'd bring to the job. Thank you for considering my application.

Tetovo, North Macedonia , 10 Jan 2022

Liridon Ceka

Alekan